

(+48) 792-656-584 michal.78.60@gmail.com www.michaljaniuk.pl www.github.com/Mike7860

# Michał Janiuk

## **PYTHON SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

#### ABOUT ME

My greatest interest is personal development. I've got experience as a HbbTV and SI / PSI tester, but from 3 years I have decided to develop myself as a developer. I like learning mainly backend technologies and also frontend technologies. Python is my favorite programming language.

# **SKILLS**

PYTHON - intermediate level

HTML5 - intermediate level

CSS3 - intermediate level

SQL - intermediate level

**DJANGO** - basic level

FLASK - basic level

GIT - basic level

LINUX - basic level

AWS - basic level

DOCKER - basic level

ENGLISH - intermediate level

# **HOBBY**

Personal development, dancing, healthy lifestyle, team sports, playing guitar, cooking

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2022.06 - NOW *SOFTSERVE* 

**PYTHON DEVELOPER** 

Bug fixing, working with Flask, new functionalities etc.

2021.10 - 2022.05 AVENGA AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

Preparing automation tools in Phantom (Python), working with API, data processing etc.

2021.04 – 2021.09 FINITEC SP. Z.O.O PYTHON DEVELOPER

Data processing, new functionalities, code refactoring, working with graphs, regular expressions, NLP etc.

2017.09 – 2020.12 SAMSUNG ELECTRONICS JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Testing HbbTV, SI / PSI, creating test automation tools in Python (using the Flask framework), C++, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5

#### **EDUCATION**

2018.02

MILITARY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY MSC DEGREE

Electronics and telecommunication

2016.02

MILITARY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY BSC DEGREE

Electronics and telecommunication